blackberrycool.com 2009-06-20

# Privacy Policy | BlackBerry Cool

What follows is the privacy policy for BlackBerry Cool, which outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we treat it according to this policy, and we use your personal information only in the ways specified when it was collected. We do not otherwise share it. BlackBerry Cool is committed to protecting the privacy of our readers. If you have any comments or suggestions regarding this policy, please [contact us](http://www.blackberrycool.com/contact-us/).

### Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on BlackBerry Cool. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

### Ownership of Information

BlackBerry Cool is the sole owner of any information collected on our website.

### Comments/Message Boards

BlackBerry Cool features a comment section (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

### Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

### Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but BlackBerry Cool may need to disclose information when required by law.

### Business Transitions

If BlackBerry Cool is acquired by or merges with another company, the assets of our website, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

### Links

BlackBerry Cool frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by BlackBerry Cool.

### Notification of Changes

When BlackBerry Cool makes changes to our privacy policy we will post those changes here.
